(Sheldon:)-Hello.
-Hello.
(Mrs Cooper:)Are you ready to discuss
this calmly, like adults?
(Sheldon:)I am.
(Mrs Cooper:)Shelly, I'm sorry that
you saw what you saw.
(Mrs Cooper:)I know that this is hard for you.
(Sheldon:)I think what most upsets me
about it, Mother, is the hypocrisy.
(Sheldon:)Doesn't this contradict
(Sheldon:)all the religious rules you've
been espousing your whole life?
(Mrs Cooper:)You're right, it does,
and it's something
(Mrs Cooper:)that I'm struggling
with these days.
(Sheldon:)Then why are you doing it?
(Mrs Cooper:)Because I'm not perfect, Shelly.
And that man's booty ls.
(Sheldon:)Well, this is confusing for me.
(Sheldon:)But I don't want to stand
in the way of your happiness.
(Penny:)So...
(Sheldon:)I'll condemn you internally
while maintaining